<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Floran Root</name>
    <author>TitaniusRex</author>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<packageId>TitaniusRex.FloranRoot</packageId>
    <description>
Once upon a time there lived a Ruler on the Planet-City. The Ruler did only what would benefit. His world prospered and his people loved him. There was a Scientist on that planet. The Scientist gained fame by changing ordinary rats. Many liked pets of unusual colors and their ability to execute commands. As often happens, this was just a by-product of his research: color is just a marking, and reasonableness is humility and order. It is not known for certain who was the initiator, but the Scientist received funding, and the Ruler expected benefits. The Scientist created few intelligent creatures that devour flesh, but they themselves are plants more than animals. The Ruler received even more love from his subjects when he replenished stocks of plant foods that were inaccessible at that time. And, what the townsfolk did not know, the bodies of the deceased townspeople were no longer cremated, but used without a trace. This went on for some time. There were incidents, someone was eaten, nothing serious. The Scientist went to a new project. Control over the "garden" became worse. Whether a lot of time has passed or not is not so important. There was a disaster and many people were hurt. They tried to hush up the situation, because few people understood the scale of the disaster. The second catastrophe was fatal to the planet. The army could not cope with conventional means. They began to use fire, but the destructive force was unstoppable. Then the chemicals were applied. The planet is now home to scavengers of all stripes. The Ruler lives on another planet, his talent for building profit systems has helped him, his lands are prospering. The Scientist is gone, and his legacy has spread to countless planets.


Когда-то на Планете-Городе жил Правитель. Правитель делал только то что принесёт выгоду. Мир его процветал и народ его любил. На той планете был Учёный. Известность Учёный получил, изменив обычных крыс. Многим понравились питомци необычной расцветки и их способностью у исполнению команд. Как часто бывает - это был лишь побочный продукт его исследований: цвет всего лишь маркировка, а разумность - покорность и порядок. Доподленно не известно кто был инициатором, но Учёный получил финансирование, а Правитель ожидал выгоду. Учёный создал мало разумных тварей, пожирающие плоть, но сами являющиеся растениями больше чем животными. Правитель получил ещё больше любви своих потданных когда пополнил запасы, малодоступной в то время, растительной пищи. И, чего не знали обыватели, тела почивших горожан боле не кремировали а использовали без остатка. Так продолжалось какое-то время. Случались инциденты, кого-то съедали, ничего серьёздного. Учёный отправился на новый проэкт. Контроль над "огородом" стал хуже. Много ли времени прошло или нет, не так важно. Бедствие случилось, многие пострадали. Ситуацию постарались замять, ведь мало кто понимал масштабы катастрофы. Вторая котострофа была фатальна для планеты. Армия не справлялась обычными средствами. Стали использовать огонь, но разрушительная сила была не удержима. После приминили химикаты. Планета теперь дома для мусорщиков всех мастей. Правитель живёт на другой планете, его талант выстраивать системы выгоды помог ему,его земли процветают. Учёный пропал, а наследие его распространилось на безчисленные планеты.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
			<displayName>Royalty</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</packageId>
			<displayName>Ideology</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>epicfloor.CustomButcherFramework</packageId>
			<displayName>Custom Butcher Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2848410310</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	
	<loadAfter>
	    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>epicfloor.CustomButcherFramework</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>


